<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chashabad</string>
    <string name="title_text">Choose a Crop</string>
    <string name="main_cucumber_title_text">Cucumber Cultivation Cycle</string>
    <string name="main_tomato_title_text">Tomato Cultivation Cycle</string>
    <string name="main_carrot_title_text">Carrot Cultivation Cycle</string>
    <string name="main_radish_title_text">Radish Cultivation Cycle</string>
    <string name="guide_text">Tap on an Image</string>
    <string name="lang_btn_text">বাংলা</string>
    <string name="title_activity_seed">Seeds</string>
    <string name="cucumber_seed_text">
        "Seeds absorb water and nutrients from soil."
        "For germination of seeds moisture is very important."
        "Moisture helps to soften the seed shell. It also forms soluble nutrient that can be absorbed by the sprout by combining with the protein or starch within the seed."
    </string>
    <string name="cucumber_seedling_text">
    	"Germination of seeds occur usually in 3 to 10 days after sowing."
        "But it can take as long as 21 days too.\n\n"

        "After sprouting 2 leaves appear from the inside of the seed that are called cotyledon."
        "The plant starts photosynthesis using these early leaves."
    </string>
    <string name="cucumber_vine_text">
        "In this stage cucumber vines and leaves develop."
        "When the vines get stronger and longer, they should be attached to solid trellis.\n\n"

        "New leaves will come out of the plant continuously. Tendrils will grow for getting support by wrapping themselves around whatever nearby."
    </string>
    <string name="cucumber_flower_text">
        "About 35 days after sprouting, male flowers begin to appear on the plant. And then after 10 days female flowers do so.\n\n"

        "Directly behind a female flower there is a bulge that seems to be an immature cucumber. It's the ovary of the flower and will turn into a cucumber in 7 to 12 days."
    </string>
    <string name="cucumber_fruit_text">
        "Cucumber production spans from 4 to 12 weeks."
        "For maximum harvest, on-time picking of cucumbers is important."
        "Cucumbers should be picked before their being matured.\n\n"

        "After being fully matured in vine, a cucumber will prompt the remaining part of the plant to slow down cucumber production."
        "It means cucumber yields that are fewer."
    </string>
    <string name="cucumber_text">
        "Usually, when the diameter of the cucumber is 2 inches and length is 5 to 8 inches, they should be picked.\n\n"

        "After germination, they can be harvested from 48 to 76 days"
    </string>
    <string name="tomato_seed_text">
        "Tomatoes are cultivated using seedlings. That's why seedlings are prepared after sowing seeds in the seedbed. Cultivation can be performed by directly sowing seeds in the field. But in order to get better yields quickly seedlings should be prepared separately and then they should be planted on the original lands.\n\n"
        "For success in tomato cultivation, ready-made seeds or seeds stored in-house should be purified."
        "In a high sunny place seedbed should be prepared by cleaning and ploughing the land well. After ploughing, bed should be developed with 1 meter width by making the soil plain. The bed shouldn't be very long. It's better to make it 3 to 5 meters long. Thus maintenance becomes easy.\n\n"
        "It's good to purify the soils of the seedbed. To purify seedbed soil, it should be ploughed and mixed with organic fertilizers. Then it should be covered well with polythene for 2 weeks. Thus, many microbes in the soil dies by the solar heat. In case of lack of time, seedbed soil can be covered with 3 inches thick layer of wood powder. Then many germs can be destroyed through heat by igniting the layer.\n\n"
        "Sowing can be performed by throwing seeds on the seedbed. To sow by throwing, 100-150 grams of seeds per square kilometer seedbed are generally required. For winter tomato farming, seeds should be sowed in October-December time period. For early tomato farming July-September is the time period for sowing seeds."
    </string>
    <string name="tomato_seedling_text">
        "It takes 6-14 days to germinate seedlings from seeds."
        "The land has to be ploughed 4 to 5 times and the soil has to be granulated using ladder. "
        "20-25 c.m. high and 230 c.m. wide beds have to be prepared for tomato farming in summer. "
        "a 30 c.m. drain should be prepared between 2 beds in order to ease irrigation. "
        "25-30 days old seedlings should be planted in 2 rows with each 60x40 c.m. from each other on each bed.\n\n"

        "For winter tomatoes seedlings can be planted from November to Mid January. "
        "But for early cultivation planting has to be performed earlier. "
        "Seedlings has to be planted from August to October for early cultivation, from February to March for late cultivation and from March to May for Summer cultivation."
    </string>
    <string name="tomato_vine_text">
        "Trimming dead leaves is an important task in tomato farming. "
        "Irrigation can be provided whenever necessary.\n\n"
        "If virus attacks a tree, it has to be uprooted."
    </string>
    <string name="tomato_flower_text">
        "A u-shaped shed made of transparent plastics should be prepared for 2 adjacent beds in case of summer cultivation. "
        "More than almost 70% success in tomato farming depends on deploying polythene sheds on tomato plants in this season. "
        "Usually, the heights of the edge poles of the shed are 150 c.m. and the height of the middle pole is 210 c.m. "
        "There should be an at least 75 c.m. wide drain between 2 sheds. This eases rain water expulsion and various maintenance tasks. "
        "A huge number of flowers appear in summer tomato plants. But, high temperature and heavy rain hampers pollination."
    </string>
    <string name="tomato_fruit_text">
        "Yielding time arrives based on variant and planting time."
        "Tomato can be picked whether it is green or ripe."
    </string>
    <string name="tomato_text">
        "Ripe tomatoes shouldn't be picked for sending far. Artificial hormones shouldn't be used to ripen or to get better color of tomatoes."
        "20-40 tons of yield can be achieved through tomato farming."
    </string>
    <string name="carrot_seed_text">
	    "Carrot farming requires 3 to 4 kilograms of seeds per hectare.\n\n"
	    "Land with water expulsion system and sandy loam or loam soil is fit for cultivating carrots. "
	    "The field has to be prepared by ploughing well and using ladder. The soil has to be granulated.\n\n"
	    "It's good to sow carrot seeds in rows. It eases caring of carrots."
	    "As the carrot seeds are quite small, it's good to sow them after mixing them with ash or crushed soil. To this end, after mixing better seeds with better ash or better crushed soil, the mixture can be sowed."
	    "Each 2 rows in the field has to be 20-25 c.m. far from each other. Distance between each 2 rows is to be 10 c.m.\n\n"
	    "Germination may take 10-20 days. But germination can be achieved in 7-10 days by soaking seeds (for 18-24 hours)."
    </string>
    <string name="carrot_seedling_text">
	    "After 8-10 days of germination, all the plants have to be uprooted but 1 after each 8-10 c.m. distance on a row. "
        "At the same time, weeds have to be cleaned and soil aggregates have to be crushed.\n\n"

        "Irrigation and drainage system must be provided as required. It's good to irrigate 3-4 times after each 2 weeks regularly after observing matir joe for production."
    </string>
    <string name="carrot_plant_text">
	    "After the seedlings getting a bit stronger following germination, they have to be thinned.\n\n"
	    "Whenever the soil lacks moisture, irrigation must be performed. "
	    "When preferred soil state is achieved after irrigation, the soil has to be loosened by crushing soil aggregates using a hoe. Weeds grown have to be irradicated."
    </string>
    <string name="carrot_text">
	    "Carrot becomes suitable to be picked for eating as vegetables after 70-80 days of germination.\n\n"

	    "20-25 tons of carrot yield can be achieved per hectare."
    </string>
    <string name="carrot_rootcut_text">
	    "Each 70 to 80 days old carrot have to be uprooted. 1 to 2 inches long tip has to be kept and lower half of the root has to be cut down from each of the uprooted carrot. "
	    "Then each carrot root has to be dipped for 5 minutes in fungicide. After that in a shadowy place of the main field the lower half of the each of the remaining parts of the carrots has to be buried in 50 c.m. to 1 metre distance from the previous one."
	    "Flowers appear in 1 to 2 months in the plant. Carrot seeds have to be collected in 3 to 4 months from them."
    </string>
    <string name="carrot_non_rootcut_text">
	    "After 30 to 40 days of the appearance of flowers in the plant, the fruits gets ripen and dried and turns brown. The stalks of the fruits also gets dried. Then fruits along with their stalks have to be collected during dawn. "
        "By storing properly, the germination ability of the carrot seeds can be retained for 2 to 3 years."
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_seedling">Seedlings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vine">Vines</string>
    <string name="title_activity_flower">Flowers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fruit">Fruits</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cucumber">Cucumber</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tomato">Tomato</string>
    <string name="title_activity_carrot">Carrot</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rootcutting">Root Cutting</string>
    <string name="title_activity_non_rootcutting">Regular Way</string>
    <string name="arrow">Arrow Sign</string>
</resources>